ICICI Lombard is
known for its wife who makes the process of booking a two wheeler
third party policy
very easy
Welcome to this video in which we will
tell you about the steps to book a two wheeler third party policy Come to the Digital Seva
Portal home page and
click on the Insurance option
Type ICICI Lombard in the search option Click on the ICICI Lombard icon and
come to the Partner home page
i.e. ICICI Lombard homepage On the
right side of the home page you will
find our product options To
buy a third party bike policy
click on the WTP icon Click on
Renew Existing and Left Policies
and then click on the Get Full Quota tab
Thank you Once you are
on the screen One Registration Details to WTP page
Enter your customer's vehicle registration number
and
click on Get It On tab to get the complete vehicle details Check the
model, manufacturing, engine and
chassis number shown on the page with your RC The
PA cover on the screen to that details has already been removed from the premium rate
And TPD is restricted up to 6000
Previous policy details have
already been entered Click on No option Click on
orange gate tap to view premium Rs 828
This screen will display Customer Details Click on
blue Create New Customer tap to enter customer details Enter Customer
Name, Address, Pin Code, Email ID and Phone Number
After entering customer details, click on orange gate tap to view the
proposal number generated along with premium Rs 828 At the
bottom right corner of the page,
you will find Buy Policy option in blue colour
Click on it to go to CSC Wallet Payment page View Screen for
Policy PDF After entering your CSC Password
and Wallet PIN, wait for a while
You will reach a page
where you will see your policy number
and an option to view your customer's policy PDF